From Sailor to Slayer
Popeye's Revenge is a horror film directed by William Stead.
The legend of Popeye haunts a group of counsellors as
they intend to open a summer camp.
Popeye (Johnny), played by Steven Murphy.
Tara, played by Emily Mogilner.
Dylan, played by Connor Powles.
Donna, played by Danielle Ronald.
Nick, played by Bruno Cryan.
Sky, played by Atlanta Moreno.
Popeye’s Revenge is a 2025 British slasher film directed by
William Stead and written by Harry Boxley.
It is produced by ITN Studios, and stars Steven Murphy, Emily
Mogilner, Connor Powles, Danielle Ronald and Bruno Cryan.
The film is one of three live-action horror films featuring Popeye that were released in 2025 after the character entered
the public domain in the United States: the other two are Popeye the Slayer Man and Shiver Me Timbers.
Popeye's Revenge was produced by ITN Studios that also produced the Twisted Childhood
Universe films, though it does not take place in the same cinematic universe.
Popeye's Revenge was released in the US on February 13, 2025 on VOD before
being made available six days later on Amazon Prime Video.
It received negative reactions
from critics.
The film explores themes of gore, based on
cartoon, slasher, re-imagining, blood.
The tone is dark.